Tom Miller papers, 1852-2003 (Bulk 1950-2003)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series I: Publications by Tom Miller
  - Subseries 1: Articles
    - Fan: A Baseball Magazine, Summer 1995 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Think Globally (Have a Good Time Locally). Los Angeles Times Book Review, July 9, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Have Wheels, Will Travel. Washington Post Book World, July 30, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Cuba: Poised for change. San Antonio Express-News, August 27, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Una mezcla campestre. Dos Filos, September/October 1995 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - We still (sigh) play hardball with Cuba. Newsday, February 28, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - We still (sigh) play hardball with Cuba. Cuba Update, March/April 1996 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Sotheby's could never match this one. Newsday, April 29, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - On The Block: What Am I Bid For Jack Ruby's Kitchen Sink? Tucson Weekly, May 2-8, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Letter from Havana: The revolution will not be undersold. Newsday, June 23, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Heat Stroke (chapter nine). Tucson Citizen, July 3, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Conquering Back Pain. OneSource, Summer 1996 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Letter From Havana: The Constant Hero - A frequent flier to Cuba finds on the streets of the capital a figure more enduring than the image of Fidel. Worldview, Fall 1996 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Tu Scream, Yo Scream. Tucson Weekly, September 19-25, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Letter from Havana: The revolution will not be undersold. San Jose Mercury News, September 15, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - ... And the Caribbean didn't drain away. Newsday, September 25, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Vanishing America. Lands' End Direct Merchants. Dodgeville, Wisc, December 1996 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - ... And the Caribbean didn't drain away. Cuba Update, Winter 1997 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - On language and love. Latino USA, NPR, February 8-15, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Rebel With a Cause. Washington Post Book World, April 27, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Los Van Van: Cuba's most popular and well-loved dance band. Ninth Annual New Orleans by the Bay Official Program, June 1997 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - The Bus Stops Here. Playboy, July 1997 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Dateline: Havana. Mungo Park, http://www.mungopark.com, Live Expedition-Dispatches, July 1997 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Evening on the Malecon. Mungo Park, http://www.mungopark.com, Live Expedition - Dispatches, Dispatch One, July 14, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Grumpy Old Men and the Sea. Mungo Park, http://www.mungopark.com, Live Expedition - Dispatches, Dispatch Two, July 15, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Hemingway's Trail Mix. Mungo Park, http://www.mungopark.com, Live Expedition - Dispatches, Dispatch Three, July 16, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Dancing in the Streets. Mungo Park, http://www.mungopark.com, Live Expedition - Dispatches, Dispatch Four, July 17, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - A Museum Piece. Mungo Park, http://www.mungopark.com, Live Expedition - Dispatches, Dispatch Five, July 18, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Queries of a Nature Gal. Mungo Park, http://www.mungopark.com, Live Expedition - Dispatches, Dispatch Six, July 19, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Heavy Medal. Mungo Park, http://www.mungopark.com, Live Expedition - Dispatches, Dispatch Seven, July 20, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Weighing Anchor in Havana. Mungo Park, http://www.mungopark.com, Live Expedition - Dispatches, Dispatch Eight, July 21, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - All Things Considered, NPR, October 17, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Che -- a Cuban tale of love, war, and a photograph. San Jose Mercury News, October 19, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - That Photograph of Che Lives on in Cuba. Los Angeles Times, October 27, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - A look at ... myths of Cuba -- the Image ... and the man who made it. Washington Post, November 2, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - A look at ... myth of Cuba: The image .. and the man who made it. Cuba Update, November/December 1997 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - The Season of Las Parrandas. Natural History, December 1997/January 1998 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Fighting the Good Fight: The legacy of Tucson's literary troike -- Bill Eastlake, Ed Abbey, and Alan Harrington -- remembered. Tucson Monthly, January 1998 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Bisbeeland! Tucson Monthly, June 1998 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Remember the Maine - It has been a century since the storied dreadnought sank, but controversy has not yet abandoned the ship. Smithsonian, February 1998 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Cuba, que linda! Los Angeles Times Book Review, February 1, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Americans visiting cuba to see pope in January. NPR commentary, April 1998 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Live From Cuba. Tenth Annual New Orleans by the Bay Official Program, June 1998 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Cuban Defectors. Life, August 1998 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Who Blew Up the Maine? Muse, December 1998 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Shelf Involved. American Way, January 15, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - Mr. Microphone: America's top theatrical sound designer has heard it all. New Times, January 1-7, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - Working Stiffs. Border Beat, Fall-Winter 1999 (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Cuba's All-Stars. Natural History, April 1999 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Home Run. Los Angeles Times Book Review, May 2, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Cuban Counterpoint: Why an Aging Revolution in the Caribbean Continues to Inflame the American Imagination. Los Angeles Times Book Review, July 25, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - A night at the Las Vegas. Las Vegas Life, August 1999 (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - Elian Gonzalez: Still mum after all these years. Miami New Times, February 17 -23, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - Palabras de la Frontera. Border Beat, Spring/Summer 2000 (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - The Crown of Montecristi. Natural History, June 2000 (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - La Señora de Buena Vista. Los Angeles Times, September 28, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 74)
    - The Suppression of Salt of the Earth. Cineaste, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - In Love with a second language. Hemispheres, November 2000 (Box 5, Folder 76)
    - Buscando el corazón de La Bamba. El Mar y la Montaña, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 77)
    - Dreaming In Cuba. Tucson Weekly, July 12-18 2001 (Box 5, Folder 78)
    - Happy Birthday Bay of Pigs. Tucson Weekly, April 18-24, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 79)
    - On the Street in Havana, Music to Our Ears. Washington Post, May 12, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 80)
    - Line in the Track. Newsday, June 2, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 81)
    - Poet, Writer, Orator, Statesman, Martyr. Los Angeles Times, July 12, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 82)
    - US-Cuba Policy Potholes. Christian Science Monitor, May 14, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 83)
    - "El Paso" The Myth and Legend of Marty Robins' Classic Country Song. Country Music Today, July/August 2003 (Box 5, Folder 84)
    - I Was a Middle-Aged Anosmic. New York Times, September 22, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 85)
    - Crossing the Line. Arizona Daily Star, October 8, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 86)
    - Putting Her Hopes Where Her Heart Lies. New York Times, November 17, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Subseries 2: Reviews, College Press Service, Scripts, and Radio Commentary
    - Home Grown Violence. Chicago Sun-Times. Chicago, IL, February 1, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Greenwich Village folklore: America's mirror? Chicago Sun-Times. Chicago, IL, April 5, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Do It!: Scenarios and Tactics. Fusion, May 15, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Above-Average Nouveau-Porn. Fusion, October 2, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Ex-Yippie writes memoirs on the farm. Chicago Sun-Times. Chicago, IL, November 8, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Vibes around the world and road to Katmandu. Chicago Sun-Times. Chicago, IL, January 24, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Search for an unmediated life. Chicago Sun-Times. Chicago, IL, May 16, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Scanning the Movement in Black and White. Alternative Features Service, June 25, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Putting it On. Fusion, July 9, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Roobing it In. Fusion, August 20, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Notoriety becomes Krassner. Chicago Sun-Times. Chicago, IL, September 26, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Grab Bag. Fusion, December 10, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Good Information. Iconoclast. Dallas, TX, February 11, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Booklet Bonus. Fusion, March 1972 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Did Elia Kazan Steal This Book? Iconoclast. Dallas, TX, May 12, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Caravaneers for Warners... Chicago Sun-Times. Chicago, IL, June 4, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Caravan in Search of Youthschlock, or, How the Camera Replaces the Gun. Alternative Features Service, June 23, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - The Assassins, by Elia Kazan. Northwest Passage, July 3-16, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - "Nixon's the One". Crawdaddy, October, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - ...and a more personal trip by a young Superman freak. Chicago Sun-Times. Chicago, IL, July 22, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - News from the underground... Chicago Sun-Times. Chicago, IL, August 20, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - A new glimpse of the anti-war mood of the late 1960s. Chicago Sun-Times. Chicago, IL, September 9, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - SDS. Changes, Sept/Oct 1973 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Fingers and thoughts along a sharp blade. Chicago Sun-Times. Chicago, IL, April 21, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Disloyal patriots. Chicago Sun-Times. Chicago, IL, May 26, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - The Okies Of California. Berkeley Barb. Berkeley, CA, February 28--March 6, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Whatever became of Jerry? Chicago Sun-Times. Chicago, IL, March 7, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - FBI Files. Harper's Weekly, May 31, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Assassin Mag: sheet Sets Sights On World of Hit-Men. More, June, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Quiet portrayal of a chicano family. San Jose Mercury News. San Jose, CA, October 14, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - The dilemma of modern Mexico. San Jose Mercury News. San Jose, CA, January 20, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Red Earth, White Earth, by Will Weaver. The New York Times Book Review, November 9, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Book review. The New York Times Book Review, August 24, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Jaguars and Jungle Obsessions. The Washington Post. Washington, DC, December 12, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Tale of a Glove Affair. The Washington Post. Washington, D.C., April 7, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - A Beautiful, Cruel Country. The New York Times Book Review, November 15, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Trekking and Trading Across Borneo. The Washington Post. Washington, DC, February 21, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - It's Doggy-Dog Along the Rio Grande. Los Angeles Times. Los Angeles, CA, March 13, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Every Living Room in the Northern Hemisphere. Los Angeles Times. Los Angeles, CA, April 10, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Book review. The Nation, November 7, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - With No Latitude At All. The Washington Post. Washington, DC, November 14, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Around the World the Hard Way. The Arizona Republic, December 25, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Six about South America: A shelf of classics for discriminating readers. Diversion, February, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Latin America From the Bleachers. The New York Times. New York, NY, June 4, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - The Last Rough Rider. The Washington Post. Washington, DC, October 8, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Book review. Travels With Candor in Cuba. The Washington Post. Washington, DC, February 20, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - The Gringo's Sojourn: Literary Portraits of a Mexican Town. The Washington Post. Washington, DC, July 19, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - A One-Way Rainbow. Los Angeles Times. Los Angeles, CA, August 26, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Children of Another Revolution. New York Times. New York, NY, September 8, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Convent Girl Makes Good. New York Times. New York, NY, March 29, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Tim Cahill's impressive bag of treks. Washington Post. Washington, February 8, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Mexican images, Mexican reality. Washington Post. Book World. Washington, December 19, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Peaceful Counter Inauguration Planned. College Press Service,, January 8, 1968 (Box 6A, Folder 1)
    - Interview With Wilbur Cohen. College Press Service, May 7, 1968 (Box 6A, Folder 2)
    - McCarthy's Strategy Works for Lowenstein. College Press Service, June 26, 1968 (Box 6A, Folder 3)
    - McCarthy's Strategy Works for Lowenstein. College Press Service, June 26, 1968 (Box 6A, Folder 4)
    - Kennedy Students Form SAC. College Press Service, July 12, 1968 (Box 6A, Folder 5)
    - New Party Gains Momentum. College Press Service, August 2, 1968 (Box 6A, Folder 6)
    - News Analysis: The Movement After Chicago: On Its Own. College Press Service, September 4, 1968 (Box 6A, Folder 7)
    - HUAC Week, Part One: Blanks and Gaps. College Press Service, October 8, 1968 (Box 6A, Folder 8)
    - SDS vs. J. Edgar Hoover, Round One. College Press Service, October, 15, 1968 (Box 6A, Folder 9)
    - Has Al Lowenstein Sold Out? College Press Service, October 28, 1968 (Box 6A, Folder 10)
    - What's New, Party? College Press Service, October 30, 1968 (Box 6A, Folder 11)
    - Election Activity Wrap-Up. College Press Service, November 6, 1968 (Box 6A, Folder 12)
    - Yippie Found Guilty of Flag Desecration. College Press Service, November 20, 1968 (Box 6A, Folder 13)
    - Huacydoowackydoo. College Press Service, December 9, 1968 (Box 6A, Folder 14)
    - Analysis: HUAC to Get New Image. College Press Service, December 11, 1968 (Box 6A, Folder 15)
    - Mobilization Plans Counter-Inauguration. College Press Service., December 12, 1968 (Box 6A, Folder 16)
    - God-Squad and the Movement. College Press Service, February 6, 1969 (Box 6A, Folder 17)
    - The Labs Belong to the People. College Press Service, February 11, 1969 (Box 6A, Folder 18)
    - Youth Department Again. College Press Service, February 12, 1969 (Box 6A, Folder 19)
    - Youth Department Again. College Press Service (Copy 2), February 12, 1969 (Box 6A, Folder 20)
    - Uppity Students, Southern Style College Press Service, February 18, 1969 (Box 6A, Folder 21)
    - HUAC Changes Feathers? College Press Service, February 19, 1969 (Box 6A, Folder 22)
    - Doctor, Lawyer ... College Press Service, February 20, 1969 (Box 6A, Folder 23)
    - Doctor, Lawyer ... College Press Service, February 20, 1969 (Box 6A, Folder 24)
    - March 4 Preview. College Press Service, February 25, 1969 (Box 6A, Folder 25)
    - McSurely and the Senators. College Press Service, March 6, 1969 (Box 6A, Folder 26)
    - Concessions. College Press Service, March 6, 1969 (Box 6A, Folder 27)
    - March 4 Comes Once a Year. College Press Service, March 6, 1969 (Box 6A, Folder 28)
    - Your President-In-Exile. College Press Service, March 7, 1969 (Box 6A, Folder 29)
    - It's Budget Time Again. College Press Service, March 11, 1969 (Box 6A, Folder 30)
    - N.I.G. Program. College Press Service, March 17, 1969 (Box 6A, Folder 31)
    - Collegium Interamerican Defensionis. College Press Service, March 20, 1969 (Box 6A, Folder 32)
    - 'Tis the Season ...'. College Press Service, March 24, 1969 (Box 6A, Folder 33)
    - Rock and Roll, Then and Now. College Press Service, March 25, 1969 (Box 6A, Folder 34)
    - Once there were valleys. College Press Service, March 29, 1969 (Box 6A, Folder 35)
    - Greek Speaker Denied Entrance to U.S. College Press Service, April 1, 1969 (Box 6A, Folder 36)
    - April Action Roundup. College Press Service, April 7, 1969 (Box 6A, Folder 37)
    - AWOL in Nixon Country. College Press Service, April 9, 1969 (Box 6A, Folder 38)
    - Freep Has Troubles. College Press Service, April 10, 1969 (Box 6A, Folder 39)
    - Protest Roundup. College Press Service, April 11, 1969 (Box 6A, Folder 40)
    - Dow Shall Not Kill. College Press Service, April 16, 1969 (Box 6A, Folder 41)
    - Congressman Koch: Succor for the Draft. College Press Service, April 30, 1969 (Box 6A, Folder 42)
    - Senate Contempt, May 12, 1969 (Box 6A, Folder 43)
    - If You Got It, Flaunt It. College Press Service, May 13, 1969 (Box 6A, Folder 44)
    - Hisc Boom Bah. College Press Service, May 15, 1969 (Box 6A, Folder 45)
    - Calling a Spade a Spade. College Press Service, May 19, 1969 (Box 6A, Folder 46)
    - Vanguard of the Movement. College Press Service, May 21, 1969 (Box 6A, Folder 47)
    - Does Eldridge Cleaver Work for VISTA? College Press Service, May 21, 1969 (Box 6A, Folder 48)
    - Teaching an Old Dog New Tricks. College Press Service, June 13, 1969 (Box 6A, Folder 49)
    - Che! 20th Century-Fox.... College Press Service, July 1, 1969 (Box 6A, Folder 50)
    - Good Ole Porno. College Press Service, October 6, 1969 (Box 6A, Folder 51)
    - Brigham Young Game Sparks Friction in Arizona. College Press Service, January 23, 1970 (Box 6A, Folder 52)
    - 60 Minutes. CBS Television, May 2, 1976 (Box 6B, Folder 1)
    - Arizona, Here We Come! CBS Reports, February 22, 1977 (Box 6B, Folder 2)
    - Hanigan Case: KSNU Radio, October 4, 1977 (Box 6B, Folder 3)
    - Weekend #16. National Broadcasting Company Inc., March 25, 1979 (Box 6B, Folder 4)
    - Hanigan Case: KDKB Radio (Phoenix), September 14, 1979 (Box 6B, Folder 5)
    - Written by Tom Miller; May 1980. (A Different Miami - Part II). Note: Typescript; program broadcast on PBS, Summer 1984 (Box 6B, Folder 6)
    - Ghost of Pancho Villa. National Public Radio, 1981 (Box 6B, Folder 7)
    - Shootout at Miracle Valley: National Public Radio, October 1982 (Box 6B, Folder 8)
    - National Public Radio, January 11, 1983 (Box 6B, Folder 9)
    - Floods in Southern Arizona. National Public Radio, October 1983 (Box 6B, Folder 10)
    - Associate Producer and Writer. A Different Miami. Richard D. Soto, Producer and Director. Los Angeles, CA: PBS TV, Winter 1984 (Box 6B, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 3: Books and Manuscripts
    - Assassination Please Almanac - Correspondence, 1973-1985, No date (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Assassination Please Almanac - Copyright Permission, 1976-1977, No date (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Assassination Please Almanac - Ephemera (Includes Photographs), No date (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Assassination Please Almanac - Proposal, No date (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Assassination Please Almanac - JFK Research Files (Pt.1), November 1963 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Assassination Please Almanac - JFK Research Files (Pt.2), 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Assassination Please Almanac - JFK Research Files (Pt.3), 1966-1969 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Assassination Please Almanac - JFK Research Files (Pt.4), 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Assassination Please Almanac - JFK Research Files (Pt.5), 1977-1981 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Assassination Please Almanac - JFK Research Files (Pt.6), 1982-1984 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Assassination Please Almanac - JFK Research Files (Pt.7), 1985-1997 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Assassination Please Almanac - JFK Research Files (Pt.8), No date (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Assassination Please Almanac - JFK Research Files-Jack Ruby Auction, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Assassination Please Almanac - Lecture Tour, 1973, No date (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Assassination Please Almanac - Photographs, No date (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Assassination Please Almanac - Promotional Materials, 1976-1991, No date (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Assassination Please Almanac - 30th Anniversary Rewrite notes, November 22, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - On the Border-Outline, No date (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - On the Border -Letters of Introduction, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - On the Border -Chulas Fronteras Movie, No date (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - On the Border -Expenses, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - On the Border -Hanigan Chapter, 1982, No date (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - On the Border -Note Cards, 1978-1981 (Box 9)
    - On the Border -Note Cards, 1978-1981 (Box 10)
    - On the Border -Final Report "On the Border", No date (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - On the Border -X Stations, 1978-1987 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - On the Border -Reviews/Announcements, 1981, No date (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - On the Border -Japanese Translation, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - En La Frontera -Page Proofs (p1-p121), 1990 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - En La Frontera -Page Proofs (p123-end), 1990 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - En La Frontera -Page Proofs (cover-chapter VIII), 1991 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - En La Frontera -Page Proofs (chapter IX-end), 1991 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Correspondence, 1982-1987 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Correspondence -Publisher, 1976-1986 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Alfaro Family, 1899-1985 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -American Museum of Natural History, 2000, No date (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Art (includes photograph), 1976-1983, No date (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Panama Hat -Research Files -Buses, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Panama Hat Trail-Research Files -Calderón Family (includes photograph), 1985 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Contacts, No dates (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Cuenca, 1982-1998, No date (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Deleg, 1985, No date (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Equator (Pt.1), 1937-1998 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Equator (Pt.2) (includes photographs), No date (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Ecuador Drugs, 1983-1985, No date (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Ecuador General, 1996-1998, No date (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Ecuador International Relations, 1998-1999, No date (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Ecuador Raw Notes (Pt.1), 1982-1984 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Ecuador Raw Notes (Pt.2), No date (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Ecuador Turbulence, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Ecuador/United States Relations (Pt.1), 1866-1997 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Ecuador/United States Relations (Pt.2), No date (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Ecuadorian Literature, 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Ecuadorian Indians, 1921-1994 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Panama Hat Trail-Research Files -Exporters, 1907-1985 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Panama Hat Trai l -Research Files -Galapagos Island (Pt.1), 1899-1985 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Galapagos Island (Pt.2), 1985-1990, No date (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -General (Pt.1), 1937-1986 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -General (Pt.2), 1987-2002 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -General (Pt.3) (includes photographs), No date (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Guayaquil, Ecuador, 1984-1999, No date (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Huasipungo, No date (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Jews in Ecuador, 1969-1977, No date (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Language, No date (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Literary References, No date (Box 15, Folder 9)